wentworthdirect.co.uk 2009-09-11

# Wentworth Direct Finance - UK Unsecured Loans

This Privacy Policy explains the steps we take to ensure information about you is kept secure and confidential.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as once you use our website and/or enquiry facility ("Services") you will be regarded as having read and accepted this Privacy Policy. You must not use our website or our Services if you do not accept this Privacy Policy.

The Slice Ltd (trading as 'CUs4', '4Quick' and 'Wentworthdirect.co.uk') is the data controller in relation to the Services and your personal data. Our registered address is 25 Ormside Way, Redhill, Surrey, RH1 2LW, UK. Registered under the data protection act with the [ Information Commissioner](http://www.ico.gov.uk/). Registered number Z8414369.

## The information we collect

We will collect personal information about you which you give to us when you enquire about one of the products advertised on the website. The provision of the Services to you may also require us to store details of your transactions, together with details of your financial information. We will periodically review your personal information to ensure that we do not keep it for longer than is necessary.

## Purposes for which we use information about you

We may use your personal information for the following purposes:

> a. to enable you to access and use the Services; and/or
> 
> b. to personalise aspects of our overall service to you; and/or
> 
> c. to communicate with you; and/or
> 
> d. to process a transaction between you and a third party.

## Our Right to Contact You

The use of Company web site constitutes an existing business relationship between Company or any of its affiliates with whom Company shares information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The use of Company web site qualifies as consent to be contacted by, including but not limited to, telephone and email for changes in account status, changes in subscriber agreements, marketing opportunities, privacy policies and/or any other policies or agreements relevant to you or your account.

## Passing on information about you

Please be aware that once you use our website or our Services, you will be regarded as having given your consent to us disclosing your personal information to the following parties:

> a. the Financial Services Authority and/or other regulatory/governing bodies for the purposes of compliance monitoring;
> 
> b. other third parties either where necessary for those third parties to provide additional products or services requested by you or with your prior consent.
> 
> c. as a condition of extending credit, some lenders you may be matched with may run a credit check from a major credit reporting bureau.

## Informing you of offers and services which may be of interest

Please also be aware that if you do tick the opt-in box on the enquiry form, you will be regarded as having given your consent to us providing you with information, offers and services that may be of interest to you. For example, we may e-mail you or send you a text message letting you know how you could save money by switching the products or services you use.

If you do tick the opt-in box on the enquiry form, you will also be regarded as having given your consent to us disclosing your personal information to the following parties who may also provide you with information, offers and services:

> a. other companies in the CUs4 group of companies; and/or
> 
> b. our trusted business partners

You can ask us to stop passing your information to third parties for marketing purposes at any time, which we will do. Such a request may result in us ceasing to offer the Services to you.

We may disclose information about you in connection with legal proceedings or potential legal proceedings or if otherwise permitted to do so by law.

## Third party providers and data privacy

If you decide to enter into a contract with a third party provider through a channel on our website, the information you have provided to us together with any further information requested by, and supplied by you to, the third party provider will be held by the provider for the purposes set out in that provider's privacy policy. Therefore, you are strongly advised to read your chosen provider's privacy policy and satisfy yourself as to the purposes for which the provider will use your personal information before entering into the contract. We have no responsibility for the uses to which a provider puts your personal information once you have contracted with that provider.

## Advertisements

No personal data for example your name, address, email address or telephone number are used during the course of serving our advertising, but, on our behalf, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. This cookie does not collect personal data about you nor is it linked to any personal data about you

## Security

No data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. As a result, whilst we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information which you send to us, and you do so at your own risk.

## Cookies

A cookie is a very small text file placed on your computer by a web browser, which has been sent by a web server. It is essentially an "identification card" relating to you. The main purpose of our cookies is to identify you when you visit our website. Each time your browser requests a web page from our server, the browser sends the information in the text file back to the server and lets the server know that you have returned to that web page. We use cookies to provide you with a better service tailored to suit you. 

Cookies help you to save time. For example, if you register for our Services, a cookie helps us to remember who you are and what your preferences are. Next time you return, we can fill in any questions that you have already answered. The more you tell us about yourself, the more we can help to find information or products you want.

If you do not accept incoming cookies then the performance of our website on your system will not be to full standard or our website may not serve at all.

## Transferring your information abroad

Some lenders may require the information supplied by you to us to be transferred aboard. By ticking the opt-in box you are giving your consent for us to transfer information supplied by you to overseas lenders. Information will only be transferred abroad by us or our agents for the purpose of performing contractual obligations to you, or when you have given your prior consent to such transfer.

## Your Rights

You have certain rights under the Data Protection Act 1998. For example, we will always let you have a copy of all personal information we have about you should you request it. We may charge you a fee for a copy of such information.

If you wish to discontinue receiving email messages from wentworthdirect.co.uk or Cus4 group of companies, you have several options: 

> a. Unsubscribe from one email list. 
> 
> To unsubscribe from a particular list, either click on the unsubscribe link within the email you received, enter your email address and click submit or write to Unsubscribe, The Slice Ltd, 25 Ormside Way, Redhill, Surrey, RH1 2LW, UK.
> 
> b. Unsubscribe from all of wentworthdirect.co.uk’s email lists. 
> 
> We reserve the right to add Individual Information to multiple lists maintained by wentworthdirect.co.uk or Cus4 group of companies. To globally unsubscribe from all of wentworthdirect.co.uk’s lists, send an email to unsubscribeglobal@theslice.co.uk or write to Unsubscribe, The Slice Ltd, 25 Ormside Way, Redhill, Surrey, RH1 2LW, UK

## Age Limit

Loan applicants have to be at least 18 years of age. Applicants who falsify their age will not be granted a loan and will be subject to criminal proceedings.
